temp-share.com 2018-08-25

# Temp Share - Privacy Policy

## 1 - Overview

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used and protected by us, TEMP SHARE. By using our service (on website, web application or mobile applications), you acknowledge that you understand this policy, so please read it carefully. We may modify the content of this document/page and the agreement will become effective immediately. 

You can find the link of this document on the bottom (footer) of each page with title "Privacy & Cookies". The word "Privacy" in the link title can easily be found and intuitively describes the meaning of the link. On home-page, the link is part of the menu and is visible when you click the menu button. 

## 2 - Logs, the default information we collect 

When opening our website, by default, our web-servers automatically stores your public IP address (at the moment of browsing). With public IP address id associated the information below: 

  1. Your location (country and maybe even city) 
  2. Your internet service provider 
  3. Files uploaded (from that public IP) 
  4. Advertisements you have viewed or clicked on our website 
  5. Number of visits in general 

By default, along with public IP address we collect: 

  1. Information about your device 
  2. Browser type 
  3. Operating system 

This is necessary for a normal, optimized and secure operation. 

## 3 - Anonymous visits 

Users can visit our site anonymously, without the need of creating an account. Even anonymously we collect the default information mentioned above(Public IP, Browser, Operating System Etc.) 

## 4 - Contact form and support center 

To use our contact form or support center you may be asked to enter your name, email, message and optionally your phone number. These details are stored on our system and can be accessed only by authorized staff in order to proceed with your request. This information will be used only during the issue/request you have. When the issue/request is solved this information will be deleted together with the ticket (7 days after marked resolved) 

## 5 - Spaces 

When registering or modifying a SPACE on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter space-name, space-url, email address, timezone, space-description, space-category, country, city, background-image and passwords. 

Space-name, space-url, space-description and background-image may be public due to nature of your service and SPACE itself. 

Timezone, email address, space-category, country and city will not be published/shared and will be used only for internal purpose only. 

Passwords are stored in encrypted format which cannot be reversed to its original form. We always compare encrypted passwords to check the right user permissions for required SPACE. 

The reset password procedure creates a new temporary (a randomly one) password. This password will be sent via email and for this reason it may be stored on our logs. We suggest our users to change it as soon is possible. 

## 6 - Cookies 

We use a technology called "cookies" to customize the dynamic content served by our website. 

Cookies are small files placed on your computer through your web browser (if you allow) to recognize your computer and web browser when you use our service. Inside cookies are placed a unique ID (randomly-generated number) from our web-servers to remember certain information. 

Without use of cookies is impossible to use some areas of our website (example: spaces, support-center Etc.). Only you and our servers (when you open our website) will be able to retrieve or read the contents of that cookie. Another use of cookies is to keep track of online patterns and preferences, as well as to identify return visitors. 

Usage examples: 

  1. Check login status 
  2. Maintaining a valid client-server session 
  3. Handling upload sessions 

We may also use trusted third-party services (Example: Google Analytics and Quantcast) that reads information inside they own cookies on our behalf. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

## 7 - Third-party links 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. Please be aware that we, TEMP SHARE, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. 

To protect the integrity of our service you are welcomed to send us every feedback about these sites. 

## 8 - For children under 13 yo 

This service is not specifically intended to be used by children under the age of 13 years old. In this case, parents are responsible for their child’s internet safety. Because of the nature of our service we can't differentiate visitors by age but if we have such information we are committed to protect children's privacy. 

## 9 - Third-party disclosure 

We do not sell, share, trade, or transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information without your consent. 

  1. We may release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. 
  2. Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be published for marketing purpose, in form of statistics. 

Third-party websites or services linked to TEMP SHARE are not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

## 10 - Security 

Every connection made through your browser to our servers is SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted. This is important to protect your privacy because the information passed a long way before reach our servers. Your information (files, requests Etc.) cannot leak during the way to our servers. 

We use regular malware scanning to ensure the safety of the files hosted here. Files with suspicious content will be disabled and then deleted after contacting the uploader (Anonymous files will be deleted immediately). 

Your personal information is stored behind secured systems and is only accessible by a limited number of persons with special access on it, and are required to keep the information confidential. Storage servers may accessed by TEMP SHARE administrators with special credentials only during maintenance or other issues. During these interventions they activity/commands will be logged in order to guarantee a safe and transparent process. 

## 11 - Modify your content 

Our services allows you to change or modify information previously provided. In order to maintain a professional and appropriate content, some information require approval from our operators (Example: space name, space background Etc.). 

## 12 - Contacting Us 

It is impossible to include here all the details or situations regarding your privacy. If you have any question or concern about privacy policy please contact us using our standard contact form. We will reply to you within 48 hours. 

_30 December 2016_
